<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:ns1="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <string name="auto_select_apn">Automatically Select APNs</string>
    <string name="auto_select_failed">Auto-select APNs has failed, try picking your carrier from the preset list instead
        in MMS settings</string>
    <string name="auto_select_multiple_apns">Multiple different APNs were found for your carrier, which
        will be listed after clicking the message below. If one of the following doesn\'t work for you, try another
        and one of them should work correctly!\n\nRemember you can always get to this APN selection by going into
        Settings, going to the MMS Settings page, and then selecting the \"Automatically Select APNs\" option.\n\nYou
        also have the option under MMS settings to select from a list of preset APNs that could work instead of
        these that have been automatically found.</string>
    <string name="dl_failure_notification">Couldn\'t download message <ns1:g id="subject">%1$s</ns1:g> from <ns1:g id="from">%2$s</ns1:g>.</string>
    <string name="download_later">Can\'t download right now. Try again later.</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="invalid_destination">Invalid destination address.</string>
    <string name="message_delivered">Message Delivered</string>
    <string name="message_not_delivered">Message Not Delivered</string>
    <string name="message_queued">Currently can\'t send your message. It will be sent when the service becomes available.</string>
    <string name="no_apn">No APN specified for the app, you need to set it up in settings!</string>
    <string name="no_subject">(No subject)</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="service_message_not_found">Message expired or not available.</string>
    <string name="service_network_problem">Couldn\'t send due to network problem.</string>
    <string name="service_not_activated">Service not activated on network.</string>
    <string name="unknown_sender">Unknown sender</string>
    <string name="write_settings_permission">Starting with Android Marshmallow, multimedia messaging applications can no longer directly request
        to send messages over your mobile data, which is a requirement for sending things like pictures.\n\nTo be able to send messages, the app
        will need the write settings permission, which must be explicitly granted. Without this, multimedia messages will fail to send.</string>
</resources>